[Laughs]
[Laughs] Suck
well, suck
fast, catch me no
[Laughs]
Oh no ยoo
yo
[Laughs]
Look quickly.
[Music]
[Laugh] [
Laugh]
[Laugh] No no no
[Laugh]
Person
I am
Ono
[Music]
[Laugh]
Oh
[Music]
Yaseo
[Laugh]
Na
[Laugh] Just
a moment Ashi Ashira Aiya
[Laugh]
[Scream]
আস
[Laugh]
Eusha
[Music]
[Scream]
Ah Chatter [Music]
Uh
[Music]
[Laugh]
No.
Oh no.
[Laughter]
[Music] এ
ভাইসাব আটা লে আটা এ ভাইসাব আটা লে আটা
[Laughter] Amerihada
.   He is
naive.  [Screaming] Shall we give it a try?
Manda.
[Laugh]
Maybe
[Music]
[Laugh]
Hey
[Crying]
[Laugh] [
Music]
[Laugh]
সা
Bell [Scream
]
[Laugh]
[Music]
Anashi
[Scream]
Yahodwae
wa
[Laugh]
[Scream]
W
[Laugh]
[Music]
Oh no.
[Laughs]
Ji
Anenoji [Laughs]
[Laughs] is
right.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Hey.
[Laughs]
wow.
[Laugh]
[Music]
[Scream
] [
Laugh] [Laugh] [Laugh] [
Laugh]
[Music]
[Scream] [
Laugh] [
Laugh]
[Laugh]
Oh my
[Music] Ah yeah hey like this
[Music]
[Scream] Ow like this
[Laugh]
[Laugh] আবির লে
আবির ভাইসাব
আবির লে জলদি আাও
আবির লে আবির ভাইসাব
জলদি আাও  আবির লে
ভাইসাব আও
Ah
[laughter]
[music] I
like it.
[Screaming]
[Laughing] ক
বাছ আছে কি আছে না Yes.
[Laughs]
I'm here already.  [Music]
Yay!
[Laugh]
[Music]
Me too.
[Laugh] Do
n't come.
[Laugh]
ย
Ga
here [Laugh]
Ah here
[Laugh]
[Laugh] Ah
ma
[Laugh]
[Scream]
Wa wow ah do
well too
Ono
[Laugh]
Igo
Daki [Music]
[Laugh] Yaho
wow
[Laugh]
[Music]
Da
[Laugh]
Yano